The following is an example
of closed caption timing.
When I was a kid I wanted to be a filmmaker.
To me there was no higher artistic
achievement than that.
I watched movies all the time.
I watched all the movies.
I bought this book and the oscars,
the oscars were my Super Bowl.
What would I wear?
What would I say in my acceptance speech?
Would I do Roberto Bonnini?
Pull a Sally Fields or play
it straight like Hanks?
But more than anything I just
wanted to make great films.
I wanted big cameras.
I wanted the big crew.
I wanted the gzhgzhgzhgzh.
I wanted to work with the best actors.
I wanted the best scripts,
the cranes,
the locations,
I wanted all of that.
I wanted to be the best version of filmmaker that
I thought was the only version of the filmmaker.
The ones with F#$% bowties.
That's what I thought it meant to tell stories.